back to my series where I recreate Ben
and Jerry's flavors, but lower in
calories and higher in protein. This is
impressively fudged. Let me show you how
to make it. Starting off with a
chocolate base. I've been loving these
Quest protein milkshakes. They have 45 g
of protein, which let you get almost 50
g of protein from this pint. We're just
going to add some cocoa powder,
sweetener, salt, zantham gum, and we're
going to blend that all together. Throw
it in the freezer for at least 16 hours.
Take it out, run out of hot water for
about a minute, and then throw it in
your creamy on the light ice cream set.
If it comes out super powdery like mine
did, scrape down the sides and respin
it. After the respin, it should be
looking pretty good. So, we can take it
out, hollow out a hole in the center
with a butter knife, and then add in our
chopped chocolatecovered pretzels. You
can totally use protein pretzels. I know
there's a bunch of different companies
making them now, but they're kind of
expensive, and I know not everyone has
access to them. After running it on the
mixing setting, it's pretty much all
done. And I top mine with a little bit
of molden flaky salt because every good
pretzel has some nice thick salt on top.